Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ooh! ♪
♪ 哦！ ♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ SpongeBob
Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants!♪Ready?
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪ 准备好了吗？
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Time for boating school!
划船学校的时间到了！
Let it rip, Gary.
让它撕裂吧，加里。
Ah...
啊...
Ta-da!
哒哒！
Not bad, partner in crime.
不错，犯罪同伙。
The toasts could have been
a little darker, though.
吐司本来可以是
不过有点暗。
See you later.
稍后见。
Hey, SpongeBob, want
to go jelly fishing?
嘿，海绵宝宝，想要
去钓果冻吗？
Sorry, Patrick, I can't.
I have school today.
抱歉，帕特里克，我不能。
我今天有学校。
What am I supposed to do all day
while you're at school?
我一整天应该做什么
当你在学校的时候？
I don't know. What do you
normally do when I'm gone?
我不知道。你做什么
我不在的时候通常会做什么？
Wait for you to get back.
等你回来。
Wait a second, Patrick.
等一下，帕特里克。
Why don't you come
to school with me?
你为什么不来
和我一起去学校吗？
Hey, that's a great idea.
嘿，这是个好主意。
You and me in school together
as classmates.
你和我一起上学
作为同学。
Think about it!
想一想吧！
Wow.
哇。
Brace yourself, Patrick.
振作起来，帕特里克。
I'm about to introduce you
我正要介绍你
to the greatest academic
thrill ride of your lifetime.
致最伟大的学术
你一生中最刺激的旅程。
I have no line.
我没有线。
Behold, Patrick,
the hallway of learning.
看哪，帕特里克，
学习的走廊。
And here's the fountain
of learning.
这是喷泉
的学习。
And these are the lockers
of learning.
这些是储物柜
的学习。
And these are the stairs
of learning, right?
这些是楼梯
的学习，对吗？
No, they're just the stairs.
不，它们只是楼梯。
Theseare the stairs of learning.
这些是学习的阶梯。
Where's everyone?
大家都在哪里？
I don't know.
Home probably.
我不知道。
可能是回家了。
Class doesn't
start till 9:00.
类没有
开始至 9:00。
6:20?
6:20？
But I thought
you said you were late.
但我想
你说你迟到了。
Late for being early.
因早到而迟到。
Hey!
嘿！
When'll you start
wearing a watch?
你什么时候开始
戴手表？
And now for the room
with the most class:
现在来说说房间
最多的班级：
the classroom.
教室。
Huh?!
啊？！
And here's the chalkboard.
这是黑板。
It's the ladle
that helps us drink
这是勺子
帮助我们喝酒
from the fountain of knowledge.
来自知识的源泉。
Oh!
哦！
And those drinks
are recorded here
还有那些饮料
都记录在这里
on the Good Noodles Board.
在好面条板上。
Huh? Oh, sorry.
啊？哦，抱歉。
Attendance.
出席。
Penmanship.
书法。
Basic Desk Sanitation.
基本的办公桌卫生。
Advanced Desk Sanitation.
先进的办公桌卫生。
I'll add your name
我会添加你的名字
so you can start collecting
good noodle stars, too.
这样你就可以开始收集
面条明星也不错。
There you are.
你就在那里。
Look at all the stars you have.
看看你拥有的所有星星。
I'll never be that good.
我永远不会那么好。
Oh, now, Patrick
哦，现在，帕特里克
I'm just like everyone else
我和其他人一样
no matter how many stars I have.
不管我有多少颗星星。
Ahem!
咳咳！
Seventy-four.
七十四。
Who said that?
谁说的？
Was it him?
是他吗？
I doubt it.
我对此表示怀疑。
That's Roger,
our class science project.
那是罗杰，
我们班的科学项目。
What does he teach us?
他教我们什么？
The greatest lesson of all:
the precious value of life.
最重要的教训是：
生命的宝贵价值。
You see, Patrick, Roger Shell
represents the fragile line
你看，帕特里克、罗杰·谢尔
代表脆弱的线
between life and death
when behind the wheel of a boat.
生与死之间
当坐在船的方向盘后面时。
This lightbulb
represents knowledge.
这个灯泡
代表知识。
And without its energy
and warmth
没有它的能量
和温暖
within minutes, Roger would die.
几分钟之内，罗杰就会死去。
Life, death!
生，死！
Patrick!
帕特里克！
Sorry.
对不起。
The best part of being early is
早到的最好的部分是
you get to sit close
to the teacher.
你可以坐得很近
给老师。
Think you can handle
the second chair?
认为你可以应付
第二把椅子？
I'm waiting!
我在等！
This is gonna be great!
这会很棒的！
Hello, class.
哈喽，同学们。
My name is Mrs. Puff.
我的名字是普芙夫人。
And the only reason I say that
is because I see we have
我这么说的唯一原因
是因为我看到我们有
a new student.
一个新学生。
Young man, why
don't you stand up
年轻人，为什么
你不站起来吗
and introduce yourself.
并介绍一下你自己。
Who's the fat kid talking to?
那个小胖子在和谁说话呢？
You, Patrick;
she's the teacher.
你，帕特里克；
她是老师。
Oh.
哦。
Come on, now,
tell the class your name.
来吧，现在，
告诉全班同学你的名字。
Don't be nervous.
别紧张。
Uh... Duh...
呃……呃……
We just want to know your name.
我们只想知道你的名字。
Duh... Duh...
呃……呃……
Duh...
呃……
Duh!
呃！
Twenty-four.
24。
Oh, great, another genius.
哦，太棒了，又一个天才。
Why are they laughing?
他们为什么笑？
I guess it's just in the timing.
我想这只是时间问题。
Oh.
哦。
Today's first lesson
will be on "Turning."
今天的第一课
将在“转弯”中。
Twenty-four.
24。
Hey, Patrick.
嘿，帕特里克。
What?
什么？
I thought of something
funnier than 24.
我想到了一件事
比24更有趣。
Let me hear it.
让我听听。
Twenty-five.
二十五岁。
That's enough!
够了！
Young man, this
is your first day
年轻人，这个
是你的第一天
so I'll let you
off with a warning.
所以我会让你
并发出警告。
As for you, SpongeBob
至于你，海绵宝宝
I expect more
from a good noodle.
我期待更多
来自好面条。
Pay attention.
注意。
Yes, Mrs. Puff.
是的，帕夫夫人。
Now, then, "Turning":
现在，那么，“转向”：
what every driver should know.
每个司机都应该知道的事情。
When you are turning
当你转身时
it is important
to signal at least...
这很重要
至少发出信号...
"Big Fat Meanie"?!
“大胖贱人”？！
Patrick, you can't do that!
帕特里克，你不能这么做！
She's the teacher.
她是老师。
What about the teacher?
老师呢？
What...
什么...
As if I really look like this!
好像我真的是这个样子啊！
SpongeBob, I believe you know
海绵宝宝，我相信你知道
the punishment
for two classroom disruptions.
惩罚
两次课堂中断。
No.
不。
I'm sorry, SpongeBob
对不起，海绵宝宝
but if one wishes
to bea good noodle
但如果有人愿意
做一碗好面条
one must behave
like a good noodle.
一个人必须表现得好
就像一根好面条。
I'm a good noodle!
我是好面条啊！
You'll get this star
back when you earn it.
你将获得这颗星
当你赚到的时候再回来。
Nooo!
不！
No! No! No!
不！不！不！
No! No! No! No! No!
不！不！不！不！不！
No! No!
不！不！
Mrs. Puff,
is it nap time?
泡芙女士，
现在是午睡时间吗？
SpongeBob, I've had enough
of your nonsense.
海绵宝宝，我受够了
你的废话。
Now collect your things
现在收集你的东西
and move to the available desk
并移至可用的办公桌
in the back of the room!
在房间的后面！
But... me? But why?
但是……我？但为什么？
Because the Big Fat Meanie
said so.
因为大胖小气
这么说。
Now go!
现在走吧！
Thanks a lot, Patrick.
非常感谢，帕特里克。
Sure thing, buddy.
当然可以，伙计。
Oh, I guess I could be
a good noodle from back here.
哦，我想我可能是
这里的面条很好吃。
Now, as I was saying,
when turning left, you must...
现在，正如我所说，
左转时，你必须...
It's so hard to hear.
太难听了。
What kind of student
sits back here anyway?
什么样的学生
无论如何都坐在这儿吗？
Where am I?
我在哪里？
Psst! SpongeBob.
嘘！海绵宝宝。
Just ignore him, SpongeBob.
别理他，海绵宝宝。
Psst!
嘘！
SpongeBob, over here.
海绵宝宝，在这里。
Whatever you do,
don't look at him.
无论你做什么，
别看他。
Psst! SpongeBob.
嘘！海绵宝宝。
Psst!
嘘！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Psst!
嘘！
Over here.
在这里。
I'm trying to tell
you something.
我试图告诉
你某事。
Something important.
一些重要的事情。
What?!
什么？！
Hi.
你好。
Hi!
你好！
Perhaps this would be
a good time for recess.
也许这会是
休息的好时机。
Hey, buddy.
嘿，伙计。
Funny stuff in there.
里面有有趣的东西。
Funny stuff.
有趣的东西。
There is nothing funny about
what you did in there, Patrick.
没有什么好笑的
你在那里做了什么，帕特里克。
You got me in trouble.
你给我惹上了麻烦。
You got me moved
to the back of the room!
你让我感动
到房间后面！
You caused me one
of my good noodle stars!
你给我造成了一个
我的好面条明星！
Who cares about a stupid star?
谁会在意一个愚蠢的明星呢？
Gee, Patrick, it seems like
哎呀，帕特里克，看来
you would care a lot
about stupid stars
你会很关心的
关于愚蠢的明星
considering you areone.
考虑到你是一个人。
I'll deal with you after class.
下课后我来对付你。
It isafter class.
这是下课后。
Fight! Fight! Fight!
斗争！斗争！斗争！
I don't see anyone
fighting, do you?
我没有看到任何人
战斗，你吗？
They're talking about us.
他们正在谈论我们。
We're fighting.
我们正在战斗。
I don't mind if I do.
我不介意如果我这样做。
Fight! Fight! Fight...
斗争！斗争！斗争...
This is embarrassing.
这很尴尬。
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事？
Well?
出色地？
SpongeBob and I were fighting.
海绵宝宝和我在打架。
Fighting?
斗争？
Well, I can't believe
I'm saying this, but...
好吧，我不敢相信
我是这么说的，但是……
SpongeBob Squarepants, I hereby
sentence you and your friend
海绵宝宝，我在此
对你和你的朋友判刑
to detention.
拘留。
Detention?
拘留？
May Neptune have mercy
on your soul.
愿海王星怜悯
在你的灵魂上。
In one day I've gone from
good noodle to bad egg.
有一天我离开了
好面条变坏鸡蛋。
It's all stupid Patrick's fault.
这都是愚蠢的帕特里克的错。
I hate you, Patrick.
我恨你，帕特里克。
I hate you more.
我更恨你了。
Well, I'd hate you
no matter what.
好吧，我会恨你
不管怎样。
Yeah? Well I'd hate you
even if I didn't hate you.
是的？好吧，我会恨你
即使我不恨你。
I'd hate you
even if that made sense.
我会恨你
即使这是有道理的。
I'd hate you
even if you were me.
我会恨你
即使你是我。
That's how much I hate you.
我就是这么恨你。
I'd hate you if even, uh...
我什至会恨你，呃...
mm...
毫米...
I'd hate you even
if the lightbulb
我什至会恨你
如果灯泡
keeping Roger alive went out.
让罗杰活着就出去了。
I'm sorry I called you
a stupid star!
抱歉我给你打电话了
一个愚蠢的明星！
I'm sorry I got you in trouble
很抱歉给你带来了麻烦
and got you moved
to the back of class
让你感动
到班级后面
and got your good
noodle star removed
得到了你的好处
面条星已移除
and shot spitballs...
并射击了纸团...
I'm sorry
your apology is so long.
对不起
你的道歉这么长。
Me too. Let's save Roger!
我也是。我们来救罗杰吧！
I'll keep him warm
我会让他温暖
and you get a lightbulb
from the supply closet.
然后你得到一个灯泡
从供应柜。
Lightbulb.
灯泡。
But why does it have
to be so far away?
但为什么它有
这么远？
I'm coming, SpongeBob!
我来了，海绵宝宝！
Oh, where's Patrick?
哦，帕特里克在哪儿？
Oh, forget it.
哦，算了。
I've got to go
find Roger some warmth.
我得走了
给罗杰一些温暖。
The lightbulb!
灯泡！
Without its warmth,
Roger will die.
没有它的温暖，
罗杰会死。
Roger!
罗杰！
Without him
没有他
the lightbulb will have
nothing to warm.
灯泡会有
没有什么可以温暖的。
We did it, Patrick.
我们做到了，帕特里克。
We saved Roger's life.
我们救了罗杰的命。
Good job, boys.
干得好，孩子们。
I saw the whole thing
我看到了整个事情
from behind
my one-way chalkboard
从后面
我的单向黑板
and I couldn't be happier
with your teamwork.
我高兴极了
与您的团队合作。
I've decided to give
you each one gold star.
我决定给予
你们每人一颗金星。
Although, I'm not sure
what saving an egg
虽然，我不确定
节省一个鸡蛋有什么用
has to do with boating school.
与划船学校有关。
Boating school?
划船学校？
I thought this
was Spanish class.
我以为这个
是西班牙语课。
See you, SpongeBob.
再见，海绵宝宝。
See you, Big Fat Meanie.
再见，大胖贱人。
Hey, what'd I miss?
嘿，我错过了什么？
Uh...
呃...
What do you like better?
你更喜欢什么？
The coral bits
or the nacho oyster skins?
珊瑚碎片
还是玉米片牡蛎皮？
I like neither.
我都不喜欢。
Can I take your order?
我可以接受您的订单吗？
How about the barnacle rings?
藤壶戒指怎么样？
Are they any good?
他们有什么好处吗？
No. What will you have?
不，你要什么？
Well, uh, what's your vote
on the kelp...
嗯，你投什么票
在海带上...
Sir, let's just get
this out of the way.
先生，我们来吧
这不碍事。
I hate everything on the menu.
我讨厌菜单上的所有东西。
Now what do you want?
现在你想要什么？
Psst. Try
the coral bits.
嘘。尝试一下
珊瑚碎片。
Uh, I'll try the coral bits.
呃，我会尝试一下珊瑚碎片。
That'll be one dollar.
那将是一美元。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
Something stupid, I'm sure.
我确信有些愚蠢的事情。
Yippee!
耶皮！
Whoo-ha! Whoo-ha! Whoo!
呼哈！呼哈！呼！
See? I told you.
看？我告诉你了。
What's wrong
with Mr. Krabs?
怎么了
和蟹老板一起？
Nothing, lad.
没什么，小伙子。
Do you know what this is?
你知道这是什么吗？
A very dirty dollar?
非常肮脏的美元？
No! This is my one millionth
dollar earned.
不！这是我的一百万分之一
赚到的美元。
Every Krab's goal in life
is to make a million dollars
每个蟹蟹的人生目标
就是赚一百万美元
and now I got mine.
现在我得到了我的。
Congratulations, sir.
恭喜你，先生。
You have just given me
my one millionth dollar.
你刚刚给了我
我的一百万美元。
Great.
伟大的。
What do I win?
我能赢什么？
Nothing.
没有什么。
Now get out.
现在出去吧。
What?
什么？
Get out!
出去！
Everybody get out!
大家都出去吧！
You're spoiling my moment.
你破坏了我的时刻。
My millionth dollar.
我的第一百万美元。
Congratulations,
Mr. Krabs.
恭喜，
蟹老板。
Congratulate yourselves, lads.
恭喜你们自己，小伙子们。
A captain's nothing
without his loyal crew.
队长什么都不是
没有他忠实的船员。
I mean, a crew like you
comes along
我是说，像你这样的船员
来了
maybe once in a lifetime.
也许一生一次。
And to reward you for helping me
并奖励你对我的帮助
make my millionth dollar
赚取我的第一百万美元
I'm taking you on a trip.
我带你去旅行。
Wow! A trip!
哇！一次旅行！
I can't believe
it, Mr. Krabs.
我不敢相信
是的，蟹老板。
Where are we going,
Fancy Spring?
我们要去哪里，
喜欢春天吗？
No.
不。
Pamper Island?
帮宝岛？
Try again.
再试一次。
Oh, oh, oh!
Bikini Bottom
Folk Village.
哦，哦，哦！
比基尼泳裤
民俗村。
Better than that.
比那更好。
Clam fishing?
钓蛤蜊？
This is the reward we get
for all our hard work?
这就是我们得到的奖励
为了我们所有的辛勤工作？
Fishing for stinky clams
钓臭蛤
in a smelly old boat
on a filthy lagoon?
在一艘发臭的旧船上
在肮脏的泻湖上？
You call this fun?
你管这叫好玩？
Aw, come on now, Squidward
噢，来吧，章鱼哥
three fellas at sea
with nothing to do
三个小伙子在海上
无事可做
but throw their lines
in the water
但抛出他们的台词
在水中
catch a few clams
and then throw them back.
抓几只蛤蜊
然后把它们扔回去。
Don't you think that's fun?
你不觉得这很有趣吗？
No.
不。
And to think I could be wearing
a powdered wig right now.
想到我可以穿着
现在有一顶撒了粉的假发。
Hey, Squidward,
you want me to
cast out over here
嘿，章鱼哥，
你想让我
被赶到这里
so you can watch me?
所以你可以看着我吗？
How about you
cast out over there
你呢
被赶到那边
so I can ignore you.
这样我就可以无视你了。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, watch where
you're swinging that...
嘿，看哪里
你正在摇摆那个...
SpongeBob
海绵宝宝
be careful with...
小心...
Okay, I've had enough.
好吧，我受够了。
Oh, Squidward,
you got to lighten up.
哦，章鱼哥，
你必须放松一点。
Sure, the lad's a bit overeager
当然，这小伙子有点太急躁了
but you've got to learn
但你必须学习
to roll with the punches.
与时俱进。
Go with the flow.
随波逐流。
And don't bring anything
on the boat
并且不要带任何东西
在船上
that you ain't prepared to lose.
你不准备失去。
Ooh! Ugh!
哦！啊!
Me millionth dollar!
我的第一百万美元！
SpongeBob
海绵宝宝
wait!
等待！
SpongeBob, you hooked
me millionth dollar
海绵宝宝，你着迷了
我的第一百万美元
on the back swing.
在后面的秋千上。
Reel it in before I keelhaul ya.
在我龙骨拖你之前把它卷起来。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
SpongeBob, quick, reel it in!
海绵宝宝，快点，把它卷起来！
Can't you hear the music?
你听不到音乐吗？
That's a 4/4 string
ostinato in D minor.
这是4/4弦
D小调固定音。
Every sailor knows
that means death.
每个水手都知道
这意味着死亡。
Reel it in before it's too late.
在为时已晚之前把它卷起来。
Hurry, SpongeBob!
快点，海绵宝宝！
The music's getting faster!
音乐越来越快了！
There you are,
you stinking bilge rats!
你在那里，
你们这些臭臭的舱底老鼠！
Stop playing that music!
别再播放那个音乐了！
Stop it, please!
请停止吧！
I'm begging you.
我求你了。
Come on, honey.
You can make it!
来吧，亲爱的。
你可以的！
Swim faster!
游得更快！
Come to me, baby!
到我这里来吧，宝贝！
Come on back!
回来吧！
Hurry, SpongeBob!
快点，海绵宝宝！
Here she comes.
她来了。
Oh, please, please,
please, please.
哦，拜托，拜托，
拜托，拜托。
Please, please, please.
拜托，拜托，拜托。
She made it!
她做到了！
Yeah!
是的！
Oh, oh! Oh, ho-ho!
哦，哦！哦，嗬嗬！
For a second or two,
I thought she was a goner.
一两秒钟，
我以为她已经死了。
So, some trip, hey, Mr. Krabs?
那么，去旅行吧，嘿，蟹老板？
Oh, Squidward
哦，章鱼哥
you're never going
to believe it.
你永远不会去
相信它。
A giant blue-lipped clam
ate me millionth dollar!
巨大的蓝唇蛤
吃了我一百万美元！
I lost me dollar
我失去了我的美元
and I'll never get it back.
我永远不会把它拿回来。
Never, never, never, never.
永远，永远，永远，永远。
I've never seen Mr. Krabs
so broken up.
我从没见过蟹老板
就这样分手了。
Oh, please.
哦，拜托。
He's such a drama queen.
他真是一位戏剧女王。
Come on,
Mr. Krabs.
来吧，
蟹老板。
Drop the act.
放弃这个行为。
Mr. Krabs, it's
just a stupid dollar.
蟹老板，是
只是一块愚蠢的美元。
For Pete's sake,
Mr. Krabs
为了皮特的缘故，
蟹老板先生
suck it up!
吸干它！
Mr. Krabs.
蟹老板。
Okay, okay,
Mr. Krabs.
好吧，好吧，
蟹老板。
We'll help you get
your dollar back.
我们将帮助您获得
你的美元回来了。
You will?
你会？
Great!
伟大的！
Wait right here.
就在这里等一下。
Here's where clam fishing
gets serious.
这里是钓蛤蜊的地方
变得严肃起来。
Okay, you boys man
the fishing poles.
好吧，你们这些男孩子
钓鱼竿。
And I'll keep me eyes peeled
for Old Blue Lip.
我会睁大眼睛
为老蓝唇。
Aye-aye, Captain.
是的，船长。
And remember, we don't leave
until we catch that clam
请记住，我们不会离开
直到我们抓住那只蛤蜊
and rescue me dollar.
救救我美元。
That's it.
就是这样。
I'm finished.
我完成了。
We've been here for three days
我们已经在这里三天了
and haven't gotten a nibble.
并且还没有被咬过。
This is hopeless!
这是没有希望的！
Yeah. And I've got to get home
to feed Gary.
是的。我得回家了
去喂加里。
We're going to die out here
我们会死在这里
just because a clam ate
Mr. Krabs' stupid dollar.
只因为蛤蜊吃了
螃蟹先生那愚蠢的美元。
Well, if he wants
his dollar back
好吧，如果他愿意的话
他的美元回来
I say we give it to him.
我说我们把它给他。
Know what I mean?
知道我的意思吗？
Huh? Huh? Huh?
啊？啊？啊？
Oh, I get you.
哦，我明白了。
Mr. Krabs,
Mr. Krabs.
蟹老板先生，
蟹老板。
Look what we got!
看看我们得到了什么！
Oh, could it be?
噢，可能是这样吗？
Me millionth dollar!
我的第一百万美元！
Whoa.
哇哦。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
This isn't me millionth dollar.
这不是我的第一百万美元。
This is an ordinary dollar
这是一枚普通的美元
that's been crumpled up
那已经被弄皱了
torn slightly,
soaked in the lagoon
轻微撕破，
浸泡在泻湖中
and kissed with Coral Blue
Number Two Semi-gloss Lipstick.
并与珊瑚蓝接吻
二号半光泽唇膏。
Actually, it's Coral Blue
Number Three.
其实是珊瑚蓝
第三。
I trusted you,
and you gave me this!
我信任你，
你给了我这个！
I can't believe
我不敢相信
me own crew would betray me
like this.
我自己的船员会背叛我
像这样。
No. Uh-uh.
不，呃呃。
No. We will not
be swayed by
tears anymore.
不，我们不会
被影响
眼泪不再了。
I see.
我懂了。
Then I guess I have no choice
but to offer a reward.
那我想我别无选择
但要提供奖励。
You're kidding?
你在开玩笑吧？
Whoo! It isn't
another fishing trip?
呼！它不是
另一次钓鱼之旅？
No.
不。
It's this sandwich.
就是这个三明治。
A sandwich?
三明治？
You expect me to break my back
你期望我折断我的背
over a sandwich?
在三明治上？
Not asandwich.
不是三明治。
Thesandwich.
三明治。
Whatever.
任何。
We've got plenty more to...
我们还有很多事情要做...
eat.
吃。
Now, I think
we understand each other.
现在，我想
我们互相理解。
Nobody eats
没人吃
until I get my millionth dollar
back.
直到我拿到第一百万美元
回来。
Uh, SpongeBob
呃，海绵宝宝
can I have a word with you?
我可以和你说句话吗？
Have you noticed
你注意到了吗
that Mr. Krabs
has gone
蟹老板
已经走了
completely insane?!
完全疯了？！
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Just look at him.
只要看看他。
Squidward, he's lost something
near and dear to him.
对他来说很亲近。
Haven't you...?
你不是……吗？
Look again.
再看看。
You're right.
你说得对。
How do we get out of here?
我们怎样才能离开这里？
If we're real quiet
如果我们真的很安静
we can sneak over
to the lifeboat.
我们可以偷偷过去
到救生艇。
Okay.
好的。
So, you thought you'd skip out
所以，你以为你会跳过
on old Krabs, did you?
老蟹，是吗？
Even after you promised
to help me.
即使在你答应之后
来帮助我。
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你在想什么。
"It's just a dumb old dollar."
“这只是一枚愚蠢的旧美元。”
"Let's just leave the old man."
“我们还是离开老夫吧。”
"He won't notice."
“他不会注意到的。”
Well, it's not going down
like that.
还好，并没有下降
像那样。
There's only one use
只有一种用途
for a backstabbing crew
like you:
对于一个背后捅刀子的人来说
像你一样：
live bait!
活饵！
You're crazy.
你疯了。
If that clam didn't come before
如果那只蛤蜊之前没有来过
what makes you think
he'll come now?
是什么让你觉得
他现在会来吗？
Oh, he'll come.
哦，他会来的。
Mr. Krabs, listen.
蟹老板，听着。
I work with SpongeBob
all day long
我和海绵宝宝一起工作
一整天
so I know what I'm talking about
when I say...
所以我知道我在说什么
当我说...
you are completely
out of your mind!
你完全是
疯了！
Get us out of here!
带我们离开这里！
Come on, fresh meat!
来吧，新鲜的肉！
Keep thrashing!
继续殴打！
He likes it!
他喜欢！
Come on, boy!
来吧，孩子！
Closer...
靠近一点...
closer.
更近了。
Almost there.
快到了。
That's it!
就是这样！
A-ha!
啊哈！
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
呼呼呼呼！
Look, boys!
看，孩子们！
I finally got it!
我终于明白了！
I finally got
me millionth dollar!
我终于得到了
我的第一百万美元！
Oh, poor Mr. Krabs.
哦，可怜的蟹老板。
Gone forever out of our lives.
永远消失在我们的生活中。
Why couldn't it have been me?
为什么不能是我呢？
Yes. Why couldn't
it have been you?
是的。为什么不能
是你吗？
Why did he have to
go like this? Why?
为什么他必须
就这样走吗？为什么？
Why did he have to go like this
他为什么要这样走
and leave me tied to this idiot?
让我和这个白痴绑在一起？
Hello, boys!
哈喽，孩子们！
Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板？
Have you boys met...
小伙伴们有没有遇到过...
me millionth dollar?
我一百万美元？
Wow! How did you
get it back?
哇！你怎么样
拿回来吗？
It wasn't easy.
这并不容易。
Old Blue Lips is
quite the fighter
老蓝唇是
相当战斗机
so eventually,
we settled on a trade.
所以最终，
我们达成了一项交易。
What did you give him?
你给了他什么？
Nothing important.
没什么重要的。
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org